You know, Bahrain rioted so much that and Saudi Arabia even came in to shut it down and they kept it moving.
They kept popping. And the president of Bahrain or the prime minister or whatever, he bounced.
So the Orient, because I'm not going to keep calling it the Middle East because that's a colonizer term.
The Orient is rising. And even though we are seeing terrible attacks in Iran, they are not capitulating by any means.
We owe Iran. We owe Lebanon. We owe Palestine.
And I think that's what pisses me off so much when I see people say, you know, this doesn't have anything to do with me.
You better fucking believe it does.
You owe those people because their lives are being sacrificed for a better world that you're going to possibly get the opportunity to live in.
You fucking privileged American.
When I see people say like, oh, Latinos, I don't like Latinos because they don't they don't like us.
Like, honestly, I'm not even tripping, bro. I'm not even tripping.
Like, I get I get it. I get why Latinos end up being racist and shit.
And I don't like that shit, but I understand it.
I understand it because I see the same the same way that I understand why coons end up cooning.
Because, you know, folks ain't cut.
And a lot of folks are like, man, if my only way of surviving this shit is I can't beat them, join them.
Then I guess I'm going to join them.
Because if they haven't been beating the shit out of everybody for a long ass time, then I don't know who has.
And when I say they, I don't mean the United States as an independent entity.
I mean, they who for centuries have been pretending to be what they are not, who have been pretending, who have been pretending to be faith followers, who have been hiding behind shrouds, who have been putting their energy into the occult, who have created systems of money that allowed them to perfect the earth's power, to use it against it.
And, yo, it's deep, but it's not deeper than you.
And that's what I'm trying to get us all to realize.
We're deep, man.
Some folks ain't.
But a lot of us have been here before.
You know, like the dogs that can use the buttons.
Support a real one.